{
    "id": "e290682d43c145d1af99c721b8d68adc",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz # 3",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "392f9bd9f277490493674f32010fe5ea",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He died ………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We usually go and see Granny ……………………… Sundays.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We will meet again ……………………… a month’s time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you see the helicopter ……………………… the palace?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have to be ……………………… 18 to see that film.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We walked right ……………………… the desert.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "through",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Summit of Everest is about 8000 meters ……………………… sea level.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw the child running ……………………… the road.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "on",
                        "along"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Stop standing ……………………… and do some work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "about",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Bowness is ……………………… Lake Windermere.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "above",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}